export const data = [
    {
        question: "Which one is these is 'Woman/lady",
        option1: "Ha",
        option2: "Ngor",
        option3: "Nyapoi",
        ans: 3
    },
    {
        question: "How do you say 'Axe'",
        option1: "Koni",
        option2: "Kenya",
        option3: "Ha",
        ans: 1
    },
    {
        question: "How do you say 'Walk'",
        option1: "Mama",
        option2: "Jesia",
        option3: "Nyande",
        ans: 2
    },
    {
        question: "How do you say 'Work'",
        option1: "Yie",
        option2: "Ngeingei",
        option3: "Hini",
        ans: 2
    },
    {
        question: "How do you say 'today'",
        option1: "Hini",
        option2: "Keke",
        option3: "Ha",
        ans: 3
    },
    {
        question: "How do you say 'Husband'",
        option1: "Hini",
        option2: "Wehl nain dat",
        option3: "Padi kusheh-O",
        ans: 1
    },
    {
        question: "How do you say 'Father'",
        option1: "Mama",
        option2: "Keke",
        option3: "Yie",
        ans: 2
    },
    {
        question: "How do you say 'child'",
        option1: "Koo",
        option2: "Ndake",
        option3: "Ndopo",
        ans: 3
    },
    {
        question: "How do you say 'broom'",
        option1: "Kpakpa",
        option2: "Magoi",
        option3: "Navoi",
        ans: 1
    },
    {
        question: "How do you say 'Come out'",
        option1: "Lavai",
        option2: "Nuu",
        option3: "Gbua",
        ans: 3
    },
    
]